Space is a lonely town
The American Astronaut is a action, comedy, science
fiction film directed by Cory McAbee.
Samual Curtis's first mission in this bizarre science fiction musical
comedy requires him to take a cat to a saloon on an asteroid.
There, he meets his former dance partner (the Blueberry Pirate) and collects
his payment: a device capable of producing a Real Live Girl.
Including music by alternative rock group The Billy Nayer Show, this
film began life as a live show with a loyal following.
Blueberry Pirate, played by Joshua Taylor.
The Boy Who Actually Saw a Woman's Breast, played by Greg Russell Cook.
Professor Hess, played by Rocco Sisto.
The Silverminer, played by Cory McAbee.
Bodysuit, played by James Ransone.
Cloris, played by Annie Golden.
The American Astronaut is a 2001 space Western musical
film directed by and starring Cory McAbee.
The film is set in a fictitious past, in which space
travel is pioneered by roughnecks.
The film was released on DVD in the spring of 2005.
The band Billy Nayer Show, helmed by McAbee, wrote
and performed the film's soundtrack.
The film explores themes of breast, space western, astronaut.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.